365login.com 2015-04-08

# 365 login

Thank you for visiting our web site. This website is administered by Run IT Remote B.V., address: De Run 4308, 5503 LN, Veldhoven, The Netherlands. This privacy policy tells you how we use personal information collected at this site. Please read this privacy policy before using the site or submitting any personal information. By using the site, you are accepting the practices described in this privacy policy. These practices may be changed. You are encouraged to review the privacy policy whenever you visit the site to make sure that you understand how any personal information you provide will be used. 

**Collection of Information**

We may collect personally identifiable information, like names, postal addresses, email addresses, etc., when voluntarily submitted by our visitors. The information you provide is used to fulfill your specific request. This information is only used to fulfill your specific request, unless you give us permission to use it in another manner. 

**Cookie/Tracking Technology**

The Site may use cookie and tracking technology depending on the features offered. Cookie and tracking technology are useful for gathering information such as browser type and operating system, tracking the number of visitors to the Site, and understanding how visitors use the Site. Cookies can also help customize the Site for visitors. Personal information cannot be collected via cookies and other tracking technology, however, if you previously provided personally identifiable information, cookies may be tied to such information. Aggregate cookie and tracking information may be shared with third parties. 

Third party vendors integrated on our Site, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on a user’s prior visits to websites and our Site. You can find more information about Google’s use of cookies, and how to opt-out for them here: http://www.google.com/policies/technologies/ads/ 

**Distribution of Information**

We may share information with governmental agencies or other companies assisting us in fraud prevention or investigation. We may do so when: (1) permitted or required by law; or, (2) trying to protect against or prevent actual or potential fraud or unauthorized transactions; or, (3) investigating fraud which has already taken place. The information is not provided to these companies for marketing purposes. 

**Commitment to Data Security**

Your personally identifiable information is kept secure. Only authorized employees, agents and contractors (who have agreed to keep information secure and confidential) have access to this information. 

**Privacy Contact Information**

If you have any questions, concerns, or comments about our privacy policy you may contact us using the information below: 

By e-mail: info@runitremote.nl  
By mail: Run IT Remote B.V., De Run 4308, 5503 LN, Veldhoven, The Netherlands.  
We reserve the right to make changes to this policy. Any changes to this policy will be posted.
